## Vivian rishi Arielesus, Front end Developer

 $+1\ 416\text{-}553\text{-}6150, rishivivian} 1999@gmail.com$ 

LINKS	<u>LinkedIn</u>	
PROFILE	Experienced Front End Developer with over 1 year of hands-on. Committed to continuous learning, growth, and excelling in the IT industry. Eager to secure a role as a Front End Developer, utilizing proficiency in my skills to elevate application development and user interactions.	
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY		
May 2023 — Aug 2023	Software developer intern - Team Lead , MRKTBOX Toront	
	<ol> <li>Leading a team of 4 developers to develop a web application on the MRKTBOX platform using Typescript, Python and Django, driving continuous improvement in productivity and project efficiency using agile methodology.</li> <li>Conducting regular code reviews and providing constructive feedback to team members, resulting in improved code quality and reduced bugs.</li> </ol>	
EDUCATION		
Sep 2023 — Oct 2023	Information technology solutions (Post graduate certificate), Humber College Toronto	
	Graduated with Good standing honours of 73.6%.	
Jun 2018 — Apr 2020	Bachelor's in Computer Science, Loyola College Chenna	
	Graduated with High Honours of 79%.	
SKILLS	MySQL	React
	HTML5	Git
	CSS	Node.js
	ES6 JavaScript	Angular
	TypeScript	Redux
ACADEMIC EXPERIENCE		
Jan 2022 — Aug 2023	Web development projects	Toron
	<ol> <li>Designed and built a static web page oriented for the Gaming community, using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.</li> <li>Built a News, Weather &amp; Stock forecast website as a Group Project using React and Angular with an API Driven key.</li> </ol>	
CERTFICATES		
Sep 2023 — Sep 2023	JavaScript Basics for Beginners,	Toron
Oct 2023 — Oct 2023	TypeScript Beginner to Advanced	Toron